

PROFILE

Detail-oriented and knowledgeable Data Analyst with extensive experience with relational databases. Proficient on data querying techniques on MS SQL/PostgreSQL such as grouping data, correlated subqueries and window functions. Possess great analytical skills and well-developed time management abilities. Accustomed to working in fast-paced business environments.

CONTACT

PHONE: 772-202-8017

LINKEDIN:

www.linkedin.com/in/camilolb

LOCATION: Miami, FL

EMAIL:

camilolb@gmail.com

CERTIFICATES

Six Sigma Green Belt

HOBBIES

Economics Music Netflix

CAMILO LEON

INDUSTRIAL ENGINEER

EDUCATION

Florida State University

April 2011

Bachelor of Science – Industrial Engineering

EXPERIENCE

Jr Project Manager – Bayview Loan Servicing

March 2019 - Present

- Lead meetings to gather business and system requirements
- Define, review & adjust strategies of projects with Project Sponsors.
- Generate and maintain project plans (MS project) to ensure timely execution of project milestones.
- Write business requirements for Business Intelligence (BI) reports.
- Perform BI research (SQL) and provide findings to senior management.
- Validate BI reports for data integrity, quality and accuracy.

Process Improvement Engineer II – Bayview Loan Servicing

July 2013 - March 2019

- Presented, facilitated and lead process improvement activities using data gathering, data analysis and problem-solving skill sets.
- Design Tableau dashboard to track process performance metrics.

Process Improvement Analyst – Nature's Products Inc

July 2011 - July 2013

- Developed BI reports (SAP Crystal Reports) to track KPI's.
- Worked with technical staff and business partners to translate business requirements into technical requirements.

SKILLS

